Guide to the Empire State Pride Agenda records, 1990-2013
Empire State Pride Agenda records, 1990-2013
- Series IV. Audio Visual and Digital Media
  - Videos
    - Alan at ESPA Tape 2, July 20, 2006; Mini-DV V-7348 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 124
    - Willimina Interview, 2006; Mini-DV V-7349 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 125
    - Tivo Footage, 2006; Mini-DV V-7350 (Box 8)
    - Lobby DUD Tape 1, April 3, 2007; Mini-DV V-7351 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 201
    - Lobby DUD Tape 2, April 3, 2007; Mini-DV V-7352 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 202
    - Guy, April 23, 2007; Mini-DV V-7353 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 203
    - EJ Day Guy Tape 1, May 1, 2007; Mini-DV V-7354 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 204
    - EJ Day Guy Tape 2, May 1, 2007; Mini-DV V-7355 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 205
    - EJ Day Guy Tape 3, May 1, 2007; Mini-DV V-7356 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 206
    - EJ Day Guy Tape 4, May 1, 2007; Mini-DV V-7357 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 207
    - EJ Day Dan Tape 1, May 1, 2007; Mini-DV V-7358 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 208
    - EJ Day Dan Tape 2, May 1, 2007; Mini-DV V-7359 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 209
    - EJ Day Dan Tape 3, May 1, 2007; Mini-DV V-7360 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 210
    - Gov. Spitzer Address, May 17, 2007; Mini-DV V-7361 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 211
    - Marriage Vote 2, June 19, 2007; Mini-DV V-7362 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 212
    - Marriage Vote 1, June 19, 2007; Mini-DV V-7363 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 213
    - Marriage Vote 3, June 19, 2007; Mini-DV V-7364 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 214
    - Gay Pride, Alan Interview, Assembly Vote, June 2007; Mini-DV V-7365 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 220
    - Jeff at Training, July 2007; Mini-DV V-7366 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 221
    - Brooklyn Shoot Guy Tape 1, July 23, 2007; Mini-DV V-7367 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 222
    - Brooklyn Shoot Guy Tape 2, July 23, 2007; Mini-DV V-7368 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 223
    - Rockville Tape 1, August 9, 2007; Mini-DV V-7369 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 224
    - Rockville Tape 2, August 9, 2007; Mini-DV V-7370 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 225
    - TWL #1, May 19, 2007; Mini-DV V-7371 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 226
    - TWL #2, May 19, 2007; Mini-DV V-7372 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 227
    - MW #1, May 19, 2007; Mini-DV V-7373 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 228
    - MW #2, May 19, 2007; Mini-DV V-7374 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 229
    - MW #3, May 19, 2007; Mini-DV V-7375 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 230
    - Rochester #1, August 22, 2007; Mini-DV V-7376 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 232
    - Rochester #2, August 22, 2007; Mini-DV V-7377 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 233
    - Rochester #3, August 23, 2007; Mini-DV V-7378 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 234
    - Rochester #4, August 23, 2007; Mini-DV V-7379 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 235
    - Alan Interview, September 18, 2007; Mini-DV V-7380 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 236
    - Luis Shoot- GSA Meeting/School, September 20, 2007; Mini-DV V-7381 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 237
    - EJ Day Tape 1, April 29, 2008; Mini-DV V-7382 (Box 8)
    - EJ Day Tape 2, April 29, 2008; Mini-DV V-7383 (Box 8)
      Includes note- "5oop Bite- 0:10:44- Pride Agenda is the leader."
    - T. Hayward, July 31, 2008; Mini-DV V-7384 (Box 8)
    - Interviews, 2008; Mini-DV V-7385 (Box 8)
    - 2008, Mini-DV V-7386 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 104C
    - ESPA Dubs/Bumps for Youtube, 2008; Mini-DV V-7387 (Box 8)
      Giuliani- 2 NYI clips and 2001 Fall Dinner Speech, Clinton 2000/2003 speech- Fall Dinner // also incl. note: "01:01:08- Giuliani 'There are things we disagree about.', 02:08:15- Domestic partnership NYC now has one of the most sweeping…, 06:00:00- Intro to Hillary Clinton, 07:20 Hillary so wonderful to be here"
    - EJ Day 1, April 28, 2009; Mini-DV V-7388 (Box 8)
    - EJ Day 2, April 28, 2009; Mini-DV V-7389 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: Meetings with legislators
    - EJ Day 3, April 28, 2009; Mini-DV V-7390 (Box 8)
    - EJ Day 4, April 28, 2009; Mini-DV V-7391 (Box 8)
    - Interviews Tape 1, August 26, 2009; Mini-DV V-7392 (Box 8)
    - Interviews Tape 2, 2009; Mini-DV V-7393 (Box 8)
      Alan interview
    - Interviews Tape 3, 2009; Mini-DV V-7394 (Box 8)
      Staff interviews
    - Interviews Tape 4, 2009; Mini-DV V-7395 (Box 8)
    - Interviews Tape 5, 2009; Mini-DV V-7396 (Box 8)
    - Staff Interviews, 2009; Mini-DV V-7397 (Box 8)
    - Phone bank, 2009; Mini-DV V-7398 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 301
    - Boston Interviews Tape 1, March 24, 2009; Mini-DV V-7399 (Box 8)
      Bishot Shaw & Minister Walker, DP: V.Venturella
      ESPA Number: ESP2-101
    - Boston Interviews Tape 2, March 24, 2009; Mini-DV V-7400 (Box 8)
      Nancy Taylor, DP: V. Venturella
      ESPA Number: ESP2-102
    - New Alan Van Capelle Vos, September 29, 2003; Mini-DV V-7401 (Box 8)
    - Alan Interview, 2008; Mini-DV V-7402 (Box 8)
    - Pride Agenda/ESGPA Interviews, Undated; Mini-DV V-7403 (Box 8)
      Interview Laura Newinan B-Roll office Westchester B-Roll Interview Ensig-Brodsky
      ESPA Number: 55579 #2
    - Chicago PR, October 16, 2008; Mini-DV V-7404 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number:
    - Gay Pride March, Undated; Mini-DV V-7405 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 55579 #3
    - 2003 Dinner Video, 2003; Mini-DV V-7406 (Box 8)
      SONDA News Clips, newsrecords.com
    - Assorted Fall Dinners, Undated; Mini-DV V-7407 (Box 8)
    - San Jose Protest, April 12, 2008; Mini-DV V-7408 (Box 8)
    - Alaska Protest, September 13, 2008; Mini-DV V-7409 (Box 8)
    - NARTH Protest Dallas, October 27, 2007; Mini-DV V-7410 (Box 8)
    - Marching on EJ Day, 2009; Mini-DV V-7411 (Box 8)
    - Tampa- Family Impact Summit, October 20, 2007; Mini-DV V-7412 (Box 8)
      Press Conference
    - LWO Atlanta, 2007; Mini-DV V-7413 (Box 8)
    - LWO Omaha, Undated; Mini-DV V-7414 (Box 8)
      Rev. Steph., Shawn O'Donnell, LWO Est. Shot, LWO interview, LWO Church
    - Alan Interview, 2008; Mini-DV V-7415 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 105C
    - Clinton/Schumer 1999, Undated; Mini-DV V-7416 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 501
    - H. Clinton/Schumer, Undated; Mini-DV V-7417 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 502
    - Gore (Bar Video), B. Clinton, Undated; Mini-DV V-7418 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: 503
    - ESPA Interview #2, Harriet Lasalles, Undated; Mini-DV V-7602 (Box 8)
      ESPA Number: SS897
    - Fall Dinner- Lavender Lights, Undated; VHS V-7419 (Box 9)
    - Guiliani at Fall Dinner- being heckled, protests outside, Undated; VHS V-7420 (Box 9)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner Tape 1, c. 2005; VHS V-7421 (Box 9)
      ESPA Number: ESPA05 400
    - ESPA Fall Dinner Tape 2, c. 2005; VHS V-7422 (Box 9)
      ESPA Number: ESPA05 401
    - ESPA Fall Dinner Tape 3, c. 2005; VHS V-7423 (Box 9)
      ESPA Number: ESPA05 402
    - ESPA Fall Dinner Tape 4, c. 2005; VHS V-7424 (Box 9)
      ESPA Number: ESPA05 403
    - ESPA Fall Dinner Tape- 4 parts, c. 2005; VHS V-7425 (Box 9)
      ESPA Number: ESPA05 404
    - President Clinton Remarks for the Empire State Pride Agenda Dinner, Undated; VHS V-7426 (Box 9)
    - President Clinton Remarks for the Empire State Pride Agenda Dinner, Undated; U-matic V-7427 (Box 9)
    - President Clinton Remarks for the Empire State Pride Agenda Dinner, Undated; U-matic V-7428 (Box 9)
    - Pride- Before Dinner, October 1, 1992; VHS V-7429 (Box 9)
      First fall dinner- includes notes on Tim Sweeney, Jeff Soref, Mitchell Klein, Robert A., Liz Holtzman
      ESPA Number: 1
    - Pride- After Dinner, October 1, 1992; VHS V-7430 (Box 9)
      1992 Dinner- Part II- Has Andrew Stem, Sandy Lowe, Laurie Linton, Kelli Cuilin (NARAL), Erin McHush, Dr. Jack Sarsolo, Featured Speaker- Deborah Glick
    - Fall Dinner 1995 Tape 1, 1995; U-matic V-7431 (Box 9)
    - Fall Dinner 1995 Tape 3, 1995; U-matic V-7432 (Box 9)
    - Fall Dinner 1995 Tape 4, 1995; U-matic V-7433 (Box 9)
    - Fall Dinner 1995 Tape 5, 1995; U-matic V-7434 (Box 9)
    - Fall Dinner 1995 Tape 6, 1995; U-matic V-7435 (Box 9)
    - President Clinton Remarks for the Empire State Pride Agenda Dinner, September 23, 1996; Betacam SP V-7436 (Box 9)
      For one time playback- embargoed until 6:00PM October 3, 1996
    - 1997 Fall Dinner, 1997; VHS V-7437 (Box 9)
      6th Annual Fall Dinner, #1
    - 1997 Fall Dinner, 1997; VHS V-7438 (Box 9)
      6th Annual Fall Dinner, #2
    - 1997 Fall Dinner, 1997; VHS V-7439 (Box 9)
    - 1997 Fall Dinner, 1997; VHS V-7440 (Box 9)
    - 1998 7th Annual Fall Dinner, October 1998; VHS V-7441 (Box 9)
    - 1998 7th Annual Fall Dinner, October 1998; VHS V-7442 (Box 9)
    - 1998 Fall Dinner, October 1998; Betacam SP V-7443 (Box 9)
      Dub from Master, RT 4:25
    - 1998 Fall Dinner, October 1998; Betacam SP V-7444 (Box 9)
    - 8th Annual Fall Dinner, October 7, 1999; VHS V-7445 (Box 10)
      ESPA 10/7/99, Tape #1
    - 8th Annual Fall Dinner, October 7, 1999; VHS V-7446 (Box 10)
    - 1999 Fall Dinner #1, 1999; VHS V-7447 (Box 10)
    - 1999 Fall Dinner #2, 1999; VHS V-7448 (Box 10)
    - ESPA Eighth Annual Fall Dinner, September 5, 1999; VHS V-7449 (Box 10)
      RT 5:56
    - 1999 Fall Dinner- Pres. Clinton, 1999; VHS V-7450 (Box 10)
    - ESPA 8th Annual Fall Dinner, October 5, 1999; Betacam SP V-7451 (Box 10)
    - ESPA Tape 1, October 7, 1999; U-maticV-7452 (Box 10)
      ESPA Number: ESPA03 427
    - ESPA Tape 2, October 7, 1999; U-maticV-7453 (Box 10)
      ESPA Number: ESPA03 424
    - ESPA Dinner/Hillary, October 5, 2000; VHS V-7454 (Box 10)
      News 4 New York at 11:00, WNBC-TV Network (SYN), 11:00-11:35 PM, 0:34
    - ESPA- 2000 Dinner Video, 2000; VHS V-7455 (Box 10)
      RT 7:33, Hillary Clinton- Hate Crimes
    - ESPA 9th Annual Fall Dinner Tape #1, 2000; VHS V-7456 (Box 10)
      Hillary Clinton
    - ESPA 9th Annual Fall Dinner Tape #2, 2000; VHS V-7457 (Box 10)
    - ESPA 9th Annual Fall Dinner Tape #3, 2000; VHS V-7458 (Box 10)
    - ESPA 9th Annual Fall Dinner Tape #4, 2000; VHS V-7459 (Box 10)
    - Dinner 2000 #1, 2000; U-maticV-7460 (Box 10)
      ESPA Number: ESPA03 426
    - Dinner 2000 #2, 2000; U-maticV-7461 (Box 10)
    - Dinner 2000 #3, 2000; U-maticV-7462 (Box 10)
    - Dinner 2000 #4, 2000; U-maticV-7463 (Box 10)
    - 10th Annual Fall Dinner (2001) with VIZcode/ Marriage Clips, 2001; VHS V-7464 (Box 10)
    - 2001 Fall Dinner, 2001; VHS V-7465 (Box 10)
      With VIZcode for Master copy on Betacam
    - 2001 Fall Dinner, 2001; U-maticV-7466 (Box 10)
      ESPA Number: ESPA03 423
    - Eleventh Annual Fall Dinner, 2002; U-maticV-7467 (Box 10)
      Includes notes on selling VHS tapes
    - Empire State 11th Annual Fall Dinner, 2002; U-maticV-7468 (Box 10)
      Master
    - Empire State 11th Annual Fall Dinner, 2002; U-maticV-7469 (Box 10)
      ESPA Number: ESPA03 425
    - Empire State 11th Annual Fall Dinner Tape 1, 2002; VHS V-7470 (Box 10)
    - Empire State 11th Annual Fall Dinner Tape 2, 2002; VHS V-7471 (Box 10)
    - ESPA 2003 Dinner Event Video, 2003; VHS V-7472 (Box 10)
    - ESPA 2003 Dinner Event Video, 2003; VHS V-7473 (Box 10)
    - ESPA 2003 Dinner Event Video, 2003; VHS V-7474 (Box 10)
    - ESPA 2003 Dinner Event Video, 2003; VHS V-7475 (Box 10)
    - ESPA 2003 Dinner Event Video, 2003; VHS V-7476 (Box 10)
    - ESPA 2003 Dinner Event Video, 2003; VHS V-7477 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 2003 Dinner Event Video, 2003; VHS V-7478 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 12th Annual Fall Dinner Video, 2003; VHS V-7479 (Box 11)
    - President William J. Clinton- "Empire State Pride Agenda", September 2003; VHS V-7519 (Box 9)
    - President William J. Clinton- "Empire State Pride Agenda", September 2003; VHS V-7520 (Box 9)
    - President William J. Clinton- "Empire State Pride Agenda", September 2003; VHS V-7521 (Box 9)
    - President William J. Clinton- "Empire State Pride Agenda", September 2003; VHS V-7522 (Box 9)
    - ESPA 2003 Pataki, Clinton, Schumer, Soref, 2003; VHS V-7523 (Box 9)
      Sheraton NYC
    - President William J. Clinton- "Empire State Pride Agenda", September 2003; Betacam SP V-7524 (Box 9)
    - ESPA 2003 Dinner Event Video, October 1, 2003; VHS V-7480 (Box 11)
      RT 7:20
    - ESPA 2003 Dinner Event Video, October 1, 2003; Betacam SP V-7481 (Box 11)
      Audio:Mono, Master, RT 7:20
    - ESPA 2003 Dinner Event Video, 2003; Mini DVCam V-7482 (Box 11)
      Master, RT 7:20
    - ESPA 2004 Final Cut, September 30, 2004; Mini DVCam V-7483 (Box 11)
      Master, RT 7:00
      ESPA Number: 652
    - Rotating 13th Fall Dinner Logo, 2004; VHS V-7484 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 2004 Final Cut, September 30, 2004; VHS V-7485 (Box 11)
      RT 7:00
    - ESPA 2004 Final Cut, September 30, 2004; Betacam SP V-7486 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 2004 Final Cut- Mono Mix, September 30, 2004; Betacam SP V-7487 (Box 11)
      RT 8:00
    - ESPA Dinner Video Final Cut, October 5, 2005; VHS V-7488 (Box 11)
      RT 6:38
    - ESPA Dinner Video Final Cut, October 5, 2005; Betacam SP V-7489 (Box 11)
      RT 6:38, Master
    - ESPA Dinner Video Final Cut, October 5, 2005; Betacam SP V-7490 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 2005 Fall Dinner, 2005; VHS V-7491 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Dinner Video Final Cut, October 5, 2005; VHS V-7492 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner 2006 1 of 2, 2006; VHS V-7493 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner 2006 2 of 2, 2006; VHS V-7494 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner- Cam 1 Tape 1 Act 1, October 5, 2006; DVCam V-7495 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner- Cam 1 Tape 2 Act 2, October 5, 2006; DVCam V-7496 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner- Cam 2 Tape 1 Act 1, October 5, 2006; DVCam V-7497 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner- Cam 2 Tape 2 Act 2, October 5, 2006; DVCam V-7498 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner- Cam 1 Tape 1 of 2, October 11, 2007; DVCam V-7499 (Box 11)
      ESPA Number: ESPA07 239
    - ESPA Fall Dinner- Cam 1 Tape 2 of 2, October 11, 2007; DVCam V-7500 (Box 11)
      ESPA Number: ESPA07 240
    - ESPA Fall Dinner- Cam 2 Tape 1 of 2, October 11, 2007; DVCam V-7501 (Box 11)
      ESPA Number: ESPA07 241
    - ESPA Fall Dinner- Cam 2 Tape 2 of 2, October 11, 2007; DVCam V-7502 (Box 11)
      ESPA Number: ESPA07 242
    - ESPA Fall 2007 Dinner, 2007; Betacam SP V-7503 (Box 11)
      RT 9:55
    - NY Sheraton, October 20, 2008; DVCam V-7504 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Cam 2, October 20, 2008; DVCam V-7505 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner 2008, 2008; Mini DVCam V-7506 (Box 11)
      RT 8:13
    - ESPA 2009 Fall Dinner Cam 1, 2009; DVCam V-7507 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 2009 Fall Dinner Cam 2, 2009; DVCam V-7508 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Tenth Annual Spring Dinner Tape 1, May 15, 2009; DVCam V-7509 (Box 11)
      ESPA Number: ESPA09 105
    - ESPA Tape 1 Cam 2, October 14, 2010; DVCam V-7510 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Tape 2 Cam 2, October 14, 2010; DVCam V-7511 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 2010 Fall Dinner Cam 1 Tape 1, October 14, 2010; DVCam V-7512 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 2010 Fall Dinner Cam 1 Tape 2, October 14, 2010; DVCam V-7513 (Box 11)
    - ESPA Spring Dinner 2010, 2010; DVCam V-7514 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 2011 Fall Dinner Cam 1 Tape 1, 2011; DVCam V-7515 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 2011 Fall Dinner Cam 1 Tape 2, 2011; DVCam V-7516 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 2011 Fall Dinner Cam #2 Before Dinner, 2011; DVCam V-7517 (Box 11)
    - ESPA 2011 Fall Dinner Cam #2 After Dinner, 2011; DVCam V-7518 (Box 11)
    - Giuliani Signing Domestic Partnership Bill, July 7, 1998; VHS V-7525 (Box 11)
    - 1999 In the Life piece on Pride Agenda accomplishments, September 5, 1999; VHS V-7526 (Box 11)
      ESPA Number: 2
    - Hillary Rodham Clinton in Albany with ESPA, January 24 and 29, 2000; VHS V-7527 (Box 11)
      1/24/00 WRGB TV6 @11 PM; 1/29/00 Inside Albany- WMHT TV17 @6:30 PM
    - Governer Pataki Signing of Hate Crime Bill into Law, July 10, 2000; VHS V-7528 (Box 11)
    - Hillary Clinton, July 28, 2000; VHS V-7529 (Box 11)
      "Inside City Hall" NY 1 Cable, Morning News WRGB-TV Albany, Hourly News NY 1 Cable
    - Sweeney, October 5, 2000; Betacam SP V-7530 (Box 11)
    - Sweeney, October 5, 2000; VHS V-7531 (Box 11)
    - Katz, October 5, 2000; Betacam SP V-7532 (Box 11)
    - Katz, October 5, 2000; VHS V-7533 (Box 11)
    - Video Presentation, October 5, 2000; VHS V-7534 (Box 11)
    - Presentation, October 5, 2000; Betacam SP V-7535 (Box 11)
    - Video Presentation, October 5, 2000; VHS V-7536 (Box 11)
      FAIRPAC Promo video: history of interviews, passage of '86 NYC non-discrimination bill, dinner shots, Fierstein, Apuzzo City Council members talking about Pride Agenda
      ESPA Number: 3
    - Dignity Piece on Channel 13 (Albany), March 23, 01; VHS V-7537 (Box 11)
      ESPA Number: 0112
    - ESPA Ad "Skelos 2001", July 5, 2001; VHS V-7538 (Box 11)
      35 sec
    - ESPA Ad "Skelos 2001", July 5, 2001; Betacam SP V-7539 (Box 11)
    - H SONDA Passes- NYC TV coverage, December 17, 2002; VHS V-7540 (Box 12)
      Includes schedule of various news programs recorded
    - SONDA Bill Passes NYS Senate, December 16-22, 2002; VHS V-7541 (Box 12)
      Master- 12/16/02 WNYT @11 PM; 12/17/02 WTEN @Noon, 5 & 8 PM; WNYT @5:30, 6 & 11 PM; WMHT "Inside Albany" @ 12:30 PM
      ESPA Number: 6
    - SONDA Bill Passes NYS Senate, December 16-22, 2002; VHS V-7542 (Box 12)
      Dub- 12/16/02 WNYT @11 PM; 12/17/02 WTEN @Noon, 5 & 8 PM; WNYT @5:30, 6 & 11 PM; WMHT "Inside Albany" @ 12:30 PM
    - 2003 ESPA Video, 2002 HRC Video, 2002-2003; VHS V-7543 (Box 12)
    - 2003 ESPA Video, 2002 HRC Video, 2002-2003; VHS V-7544 (Box 12)
    - District Issues, June 2003; VHS V-7545 (Box 12)
    - Bill Randolph Interview, July 30, 2003; Mini DV V-7546 (Box 12)
      Tape 1 of 2- note: Tape 2 label is crossed out, now V-7592 "Website Shots: GMHC/AVP"
      ESPA Number: ESPA03 002
    - AVC Reacting to Bush, August 2003; VHS V-7547 (Box 12)
      WB11/WBABC
    - News Recordings, November 18-19, 2003; VHS V-7548 (Box 12)
    - "Inside City Hall" Gay Marriage Debate with Alan VC, November 25, 2003; VHS V-7549 (Box 12)
    - Equality at Work, 2004; VHS V-7550 (Box 12)
    - Gay Marriage Ruling in Massachusetts- Ross Levi Interviews, February 4-5, 2004; VHS V-7551 (Box 12)
      02/04/04 WTEN @ 5 PM; 02/05/05 Capital News 9 @ 5:30 PM; shots with Ross talking about marriage in NY
      ESPA Number: 7
    - Gay Activism/Marriage Issue, February 22, 2004; VHS V-7552 (Box 12)
      WROC-TV @ 6 PM, WUHG-TV31 @ 10 PM
    - Segments on Same-Sex Marriages and ESPA, February 24, 2004; VHS V-7553 (Box 12)
      "News All Day" NY-1 @ 5 PM (2:05); "Eyewitness News" WABC @ 5 PM (3:05)
    - Equal Rights for Same-Sex Couples, March 23, 2004; VHS V-7554 (Box 12)
      Capital News 9 @ 11:30 PM- Albany, NY
    - ESPA "Awards 2004", May 13, 2004; VHS V-7555 (Box 12)
    - JP Morgan Chase- Pride "Awards 2004", May 13, 2004; DVCam V-7556 (Box 12)
      Raw Footage
    - Inside City Hall, May 17, 2004; VHS V-7557 (Box 12)
    - Defense of Marriage Act, June 15, 2004; VHS V-7558 (Box 12)
      WRGB @ 5:30 PM; WTEN @ 6 PM- Albany, NY
    - Causes in Common, Bridge Rally- Chris Cormier speech, August 28, 2004; VHS V-7559 (Box 12)
    - J. Walter Thompson- Will & Grace "Key Party" Promo for the Pride Agenda, September 29, 2004; VHS V-7560 (Box 12)
      #A3
    - ESPA Line, October 14, 2004; Big Betacam SP V-7561 (Box 12)
      #1
    - ESPA Line, October 14, 2004; Big Betacam SP V-7562 (Box 12)
      #3 Part II
    - Pride in the Pulpit, February 28, 2005; VHS V-7563 (Box 12)
      WHAM-TV13 @ 12 PM
    - Allen Van Capelle Interview, April 11, 2005; VHS V-7564 (Box 12)
      Regional News Network (RNN)
    - Empire State Pride Agenda, June 8, 2005; VHS V-7565 (Box 12)
      47 minutes
    - Empire State Pride Agenda, June 8, 2005; DVCam V-7566 (Box 12)
    - Allen Van Capelle Interview, August 11, 2005; Mini DV V-7567 (Box 12)
      ESPA Number: ESPA05 022
    - Pride Agenda/B'Nai Jeshurun, May 30, 2006; VHS V-7568 (Box 12)
      images of people of faith --> talking about marriage
      ESPA Number: 8
    - Gay Marriage Debate/Vote #1, May 19, 2007; Mini DV V-7569 (Box 12)
      ESPA Number: ESPA07 215
    - Gay Marriage Debate/Vote #2, May 19, 2007; Mini DV V-7570 (Box 12)
      ESPA Number: ESPA07 216
    - Gay Marriage Debate/Vote #3, May 19, 2007; Mini DV V-7571 (Box 12)
      ESPA Number: ESPA07 217
    - Gay Marriage Debate/Vote #4, May 19, 2007; Mini DV V-7572 (Box 12)
      ESPA Number: ESPA07 218
    - Gay Marriage Debate/Vote #5, May 19, 2007; Mini DV V-7573 (Box 12)
      ESPA Number: ESPA07 219
    - ESPA Luncheon and Award Ceremony, June 6, 2007; DVCam V-7574 (Box 12)
      ESPA Number: ESPA07 231
    - "Same-Sex Marriage", February 13, 2008; DVCPro V-7575 (Box 12)
      "6", & "11" WHAM-TV/WOKR-TV/CW-WHAM
    - ESPA Equality at Work Awards, June 11, 2008; DVCam V-7576 (Box 12)
      CH. 2 Audio: CAM MIC, Approx. 48 min
    - ESPA Equality Awards, June 27, 2011; DVCam V-7577 (Box 12)
      200 West MPR- 1 PM, Realm 4896854
    - #1, Undated; Big Betacam SP V-7578 (Box 12)
    - #2, Undated; Big Betacam SP V-7579 (Box 12)
    - CNN/Fierstein Roast, Undated; Big Betacam SP V-7580 (Box 12)
    - Tim Mains, Undated; VHS V-7581 (Box 12)
    - A Question of Power IFP Screening, Undated; Betacam SP V-7582 (Box 12)
      September 21st 9:20am, Theater One, Eve Morgenstern 6462855937
    - Same Sex Marriage- Alan Van Capelle Outside City Hall, Undated; VHS V-7583 (Box 12)
    - WCNY- Alan Van Capelle, Undated; VHS V-7584 (Box 12)
    - NY Marriage Examples, Undated; VHS V-7585 (Box 13)
    - Marriage Clips, Undated; VHS V-7586 (Box 13)
      ESPA Number: 4
    - "Day of the Decision" News Clips- NYC, Undated; VHS V-7587 (Box 13)
      Includes note- "good clips that show disappointment & loss"
      ESPA Number: 9
    - Comptroller Hevesi Election, Undated; VHS V-7588 (Box 13)
      On election victory and Pride Agenda
    - 1) PBS Visionaries: US-Funded International Family Planning and HIV/AIDS Programs in Kenya and India, 2) Access Denied: US Restrictions on International Family Planning, Undated; VHS V-7589 (Box 13)
    - Danny O'Donnel Intro, Undated; Betacam SP V-7590 (Box 13)
      RT 0:38
    - Dean Skelos, Undated; DVCam V-7591 (Box 13)
    - Website Shots: GMHC/AVP, Undated; Mini DV V-7592 (Box 13)
      ESPA Number: ESPA03 003
    - FAIRPAC #2: Ed Nicholas, Marc Fruchtman, Undated; 8mm Video V-7593 (Box 13)
    - Empire State Pride Agenda: The Challenge, Undated; VHS V-7594 (Box 13)
      Includes note- "Josh: Didn't know if you guys had this on file down there. We found it as we were cleaning out our office. Thanks, Ron"
    - BR105, Undated; VHS V-7595 (Box 13)
  - DVDs
    - ESPA 2003 Dinner Event Video, October 1, 2003; DVD-1327 (Box 13)
    - ESPA 2004 Video, 2004; DVD-1328 (Box 13)
    - ESPA Fall Dinner '04, 2004; DVD-1329 (Box 13)
    - Pride in the Pulpit, February 28, 2005; DVD-1330 (Box 13)
      Rochester, NY- Colgate Rochester Crozier Divinity School, Photo Credit to Frand Orienter
    - ESPA 2005 B. Up, Undated; DVD-1331 (Box 13)
      Mp-2 & Files & Elements
    - 2005 Dinner Video, 2005; DVD-1332 (Box 13)
      3 copies
    - ESPA 2005 Fall Dinner Video, 2005; DVD-1333-1335 (Box 13)
      RT- 6:37
    - Gay Rights, May 24-31, 2006; DVD-1336-1337 (Box 13)
      News recordings; 2 copies
    - ESPA Joe Tarver Interview, Alan Van Capelle Interview, May 29/July 6, 2006; DVD-1338 (Box 13)
      Tarver on WWOR May 29, Van Capelle on WWOR July 6
    - Court Ruling on Same Sex Marriage, July 6, 2006; DVD-1339-1340 (Box 13)
    - ESPA Video: "Inside the Agenda", 2006; DVD-1341-1344 (Box 13)
      4 copies
    - Marriage Equality, April 22/May 1, 2007; DVD-1345 (Box 13)
      News recordings
    - Assembly Debate Disk 1-4, June 19, 2007; DVD-1346-1349 (Box 13)
    - Fall Dinner Video, 2007; DVD-1350-1353 (Box 13)
    - Fall Dinner Video- rough cut, October 1, 2007; DVD-1354 (Box 13)
    - Fall Dinner Clips, 2007; DVD-1355 (Box 13)
    - Fall Dinner- David Mixner Speech, 2007; DVD-1356 (Box 13)
    - Fall Dinner- Malcom Smith, 2007; DVD-1357 (Box 13)
    - Fall Dinner- Malcom Smith speech, 2007; DVD-1358 (Box 13)
      With label for Josh Meltzer
    - Understanding Transgender Issues, 2007; DVD-1206 (Box 13)